{
    "subject": "resource/United_States_House_of_Representatives_elections_in_California,_1880",
    "predicate": "property/party",
    "object": "Greenback Party",
    "human_readable": "The party of the United States House of Representatives elections in California, 1880 was Greenback Party.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9868608117103577,
            "question": "Was the Greenback Party successful in the 1880 California House elections?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9222716093063354,
            "question": "Did any other parties besides the Greenback Party participate in the 1880 California House elections?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9216374754905701,
            "question": "In what year did the Greenback Party win the California House elections?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9215306639671326,
            "question": "What political party won the United States House of Representatives elections in California in 1880?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8800041675567627,
            "question": "Which party had a successful showing in the 1880 California House elections?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8566249012947083,
            "question": "Which party was dominant in the California House elections of 1880?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.703019380569458,
            "question": "What political affiliation represented the winning candidates in the 1880 California House elections?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.668610155582428,
            "question": "Who were the victors in the California House races of 1880?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6257334351539612,
            "question": "What was the political landscape of California in 1880?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.450970321893692,
            "question": "What can we infer about the political climate of California in 1880 based on the election results?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The party of the United States House of Representatives elections in California, 1880 was Greenback Party.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1434_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the political landscape of California in 1880?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1434_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who were the victors in the California House races of 1880?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1434_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What political affiliation represented the winning candidates in the 1880 California House elections?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1434_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1434_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1434_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1434_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1434_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1434_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1434_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1434_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1434_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1434_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1434_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you'd like to evaluate more triples!  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the documents, Weaver (a candidate for the presidency) joined the Greenback Party, but there is no information that links this party with the United States House of Representatives elections in California, 1880. In fact, one of the documents mentions that the Greenback Party was founded in November 1874 and briefly rose to prominence in U.S. politics, but by 1880 it had already co-opted much of its platform by the Democratic Party."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: Based on the provided context information, particularly from the documents containing information about the Greenback Party, it is evident that Weaver (who later became a representative for the Greenback Party) was indeed active in U.S. House of Representatives elections in California during 1880. The context mentions Weaver's candidacy and election to the United States House of Representatives in 1878, and his service from 1879 to 1881, which aligns with the timeframe mentioned in the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The Greenback Party did not have a significant presence in California during the 1880s, and its influence was mainly concentrated in the Midwest.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}